# Patrick Stewart

## Software Developer



## **Software Experience**

Software Developer

Nashvile Software School | Sep 2020 - Present Intensive, hands-on, six month full-stack software development program creating applications both individually and in team-based agile environments using modern technologies.

- Fundamentals of HTML, CSS, JS/React, & Python/Django
- Used Git/Github to work collaboratively with teams on group projects in agile environment
- Built single page applications using React and ES6, styled with CS3 and Bootstrap-React
- Course was held entirely remotely using Zoom and Slack daily to communicate

## **Professional Experience**

Co-founder & Head of Copywriting Maestro (formerly Airwork) | Oct 2018 - Aug 2020

Early-stage startup designed to connect working professionals looking to work on independent projects with startups.

- Acted as product manager for building the app from the ground up with designers, developers, and marketing to build, shape, and evolve the brand
- Defined content strategy and team-wide sprints while running virtual meetings

### Researcher

Sideman & Bancroft LLP | Mar 2018 - Oct 2019

- Searched online for trademark and copyright infringements against client's intellectual property
- Performed test buys of suspected counterfeit items and tested them to confirm authenticity
- wrote monthly reports to clients to detail my findings, which were used to take legal action when necessary

#### **Advertising Director**

KDNK Public Radio | Jan 2016 - Dec 2017

- Managed all advertising sales and accounts
- Wrote, produced, and scheduled all on-air and digital advertising
- Clients included Xcel Energy, The Aspen Institute, The City of Aspen, and The Aspen Airport

## **Managing Editor**

Cooper Point Journal | Sep 2010 - Sep 2014

- Promoted from Letters and Opinions Editor in 2012
- · Supervised section editors and lead weekly meetings
- Wrote articles, columns, and all headlines

970

970.456.3687

notthatpatrickstewart@gmail.com
github.com/notthatpatrickstewart

linkedin.com/in/notthatpatrickstewart

notthatpatrickstewart.com

#### **Profile**

Before embarking on my journey as a software developer I was a copywriter for 10 years, where I worked both in and out of tech. While I love writing, I didn't find myself being challenged enough in my career. I knew from working with engineers that software development would provide that challenge, so I made the switch!

#### Skills

- HTML
- CSS
- JavaScript
- ReactJS
- React-Bootstrap
- JSO1

- Python
- Django
- SQL
- Git.
- Github
- Figma

## **Personal Projects**

#### Anorak

#### github.com/Anorak

Anorak is a resource for whiskey drinkers which allows them to search for and compare whiskeys they enjoy to others with a similar flavor profile.

- Single-page app has full CRUD functionality and was created utilizing React, React Router, and API fetch calls to JSON server
- Styling was achieved through CSS, and React Bootstrap to create a simple, user-friendly experience
- Data is unique to each user

#### **Education**

#### **Nashville Software School**

Certificate, Software Development

#### **Evergreen State College**

BA, Journalism & English